# Chihiwo Thembeka Bila

+27 630 969 328 · thembekabila99@icloud.com · https://www.linkedin.com/in/chihiwo-bila-531b31200/ Free State, South Africa

# LEAD GENERATION

Invaluable experience in identifying and reaching out to prospects, utilizing strategic and targeted approaches to maximize lead generation. A strong understanding of target audiences coupled with great communication skills, attention to detail, and the ability to adapt to evolving market trends.

## **KEY COMPETENCIES**

Lead Generation Market Research Prospecting Communication
Creative Problem Solving
Time Management

Team Work Organizational Skills Goal-oriented

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

InfuseMedia April 2022- Present

## **Campaign Coordinator**

I honed my skills in crafting compelling email campaigns aimed at engaging and capturing the interest of potential clients. Managed the implementation, tracking and measurement of email marketing demand lead generation campaigns. Ensure all lead generation campaigns align with the corporate strategy and manage campaign performance reporting and analysis

## Accomplishments:

- Managed over 200 campaigns
- Got promoted after every 6 months since I started working
- 100% completion rate for all campaigns

# University of the Free State

March 2021- Jan 2022

## Student Marker

Grade student assignments according to the established rubrics and guidelines. Provided constructive feedback to students and communicated effectively lecturers regarding assignment requirements, grading criteria, and feedback

# Accomplishments:

Top 15% in BCom Honours with specialization in Marketing issued by Golden Key Society

## **EDUCATION**

## **University of the Free State**

BCom Honours with specialization in Marketing **2021** 

#### **University of the Free State**

Bachelor of Social Science majoring in Business management and Political Science **2018 - 2020**